#### Contact

farrahfaye4@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/farrah-cardona-54660b126 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing
Critical Care
Healthcare

# Farrah Cardona

Critical Care Nurse inspired by the healthcare community to pursue higher education & provide the best care possible to the communities I serve.

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

## Summary

Experienced Critical Care Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Open Heart Surgery, Intensive Care, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), and Team Building. Strong healthcare provider advancing education in DNP, AG-ACNP at USF Health.

## Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions

3 years 8 months

Nursing Instructor August 2017 - Present (3 years)

Tampa, Florida

Cardiovascular ICU

RN CVICU, Travel
December 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months)

Tampa/St. Petersburg, Florida Area

CAMLS, Center for Advanced Medical Learning and Simulation Critical Care Nursing Instructor August 2017 - Present (3 years)

Tampa, Florida

Tampa General Hospital
Critical Care Registered Nurse
June 2016 - Present (4 years 2 months)

Cardiothoracic ICU

Florida Hospital
Critical Care RN
October 2016 - January 2017 (4 months)

Wesley Chapel, Florida

Intensive Care

**OPES Health** 

Clinician

August 2016 - January 2017 (6 months)

Tampa, Florida

HCA West Florida Careers Critical Care Registered Nurse December 2013 - January 2017 (3 years 2 months)

Cardiovascular ICU

#### Education

University of South Florida

Doctor of Nursing Practice, Adult gerontology acute care · (2018 - 2020)

St. Petersburg College

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2013 - 2015)